<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>NodeJS on The Stumbling Block</title>
    <link>https://blog.ianmkim.com/tags/nodejs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in NodeJS on The Stumbling Block</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 22:50:34 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.ianmkim.com/tags/nodejs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Country Fried Steak</title>
      <link>https://blog.ianmkim.com/posts/country_fried_steak/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 22:50:34 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ianmkim.com/posts/country_fried_steak/</guid>
      <description>Co-Founder A privacy &amp;amp; anonymity centric forum for open discussion for Woodberry Forest School
Motivation Woodberry is a private all-boys boarding school in the south. In an environment like that, getting your voice heard can be a challenging task. You barely have to go through the first few paragraphs of Woodberry&amp;rsquo;s wikipedia entry to get the sense of strict hierarchical structures of the prefect system.
In such environments, the voices of marginalized identities, views, and opinions are oppressed and dismissed purely by association to the individual who authors them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cognality VR LLC</title>
      <link>https://blog.ianmkim.com/posts/cognality_vr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 22:41:52 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ianmkim.com/posts/cognality_vr/</guid>
      <description>CTO &amp;amp; Co-founder Cognality is a web based virtual reality platform that helps autistic children mitigate the effects of meltdowns and overloads. Cognality is currently collaborating with Dr. Boyd of Chapman University to conduct an academic study on product effectiveness.
About the Issue People with autism are usually highly sensitive to their environments. This is different for people on the spectrum, but in general, autistic people have unusually sensitive &amp;ldquo;sensory&amp;rdquo; systems.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>